INDRA BUDI STYAWAN

081243892626 | indrastyawan0925@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/indrastyawan25 | github.com/IndraSty

Condong Catur, Depok, Sleman, Yogyakarta

I am a final semester student majoring in Information Systems, Amikom University, Yogyakarta. I have experience in building and maintaining web and mobile based applications using JavaScript, Golang, NextJS, and Flutter. I also have good knowledge of data structures, algorithms, and software engineering principles. During my studies, I have completed several projects involving web and mobile application development. I have good communication skills, and can work well in a team. I am very excited to learn and develop my skills further at this internship opportunity. I hope to utilize and expand my programming skills, as well as learn about methodologies and best practices in software engineering. I am dedicated to learning as much as possible during this internship and hope to make meaningful contributions to the team.

Education Level

Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta @ - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Jul 2020 - Sep 2024 (Expected)

Undergraduate in Information System, 3.44/4.00

· Gemasi won first place in the AR/VR learning media category

SMKN 01 Karossa - West Sulawesi, Indonesia

Jul 2017 - Apr 2020

Diploma in

• 1st ranked student in class for 3 consecutive years

Experience

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek &

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

Traveloka - Indonesia

Cloud Computing Cohort

Bangkit Academy is a career preparation program that aims to produce high-caliber digital talent for world-class Indonesian technology companies and startups which is fully supported by Google, GoTo, Traveloka and the Indonesian Ministry of Education and Culture.

- · Actively attend soft skills classes
- · Actively attend Tech classes
- · Actively attend English classes
- Work in a team to develop solutions or applications on the topic of Human Healthcare and Living Wellbeings
- Build RESTful API using nodejs and integration with sql database
- · Deploy applications using cloud solutions that use Google App Engine and Cloud SQL

Organisational Experience

Amikom Computer Club - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022

Member of AMCC

- · Actively participate in mobile development training using Flutter
- Build a mobile application using flutter for the final project

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- · Soft Skills: Time Management, Critical Thinking and Problem Solving, Project Management
- Hard Skills: JavaScript, NodeJs, Golang, Next.Js, basic TypeScript, Flutter, SQL, Html and CSS, GCP and AWS
- Achievements (2023): Gemasi won first place in the AR/VR learning media category